<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Spin And Win</string>

    <string name="Rules">
        Game Provider
Playtech is arguably the biggest developer in the world, one responsible for award-winning series such as Kingdoms Rise and Age of the Gods, as well as a slew of other top slot games and Live Casino games. Spin A Win is in good company here, and if you’re looking for more top titles, you can find them all at Casino.com.

Game Type
Ever wondered what it would be like to step up to the stage on a Saturday night game show? That’s what Spin A Win offers, and it’s part of a wider category that includes both licensed and original game shows.

Multipliers
Spin A Win has both a 2x and a 7x multiplier, and they each occupy a segment of the wheel. You can wager on both with one of the game’s side bets, and they will also boost your payout by 2x or 7x if they appear on the spin before your chosen number.

Min Bet
The smallest chip is just $/£/€ 0.10, and you can wager one of these per bet and 1 bet per spin.

Max Bet
The betting range goes as high as  $/£/€ 5,000.

HOW TO PLAY SPIN A WIN
The purpose of Spin A Win is to wager where you think the wheel will stop. Simply choose your chips, stack them on your desired bets, and then wait for the game to stop. You can place up to 9 bets, after which the game starts, the wheel spins, and the bets are settled based on where it stops.

The wheel has 53 spaces and 8 different outcomes. You can wager on all of these and there are different payouts and probabilities for each one:

The Number 1 Has 23 Spaces
The Number 2 has 15 Spaces
The Number 5 Has 7 Spaces
The Number 10 Has 3 Spaces
The Number 20 Has 2 Spaces
The Number 40 Has 1 Space
The 2x Multiplier Has 1 Space
The 7x Multiplier Has 1 Space
Unlike virtual table games, where you instruct the dealer to “deal” or the wheel to “spin”, Spin A Win is a Live Casino game, which means that all players enter the betting round simultaneously and have the same amount of time (18 seconds) to place their bets. If you’re not sure how the game works and want to take your time, we recommend watching a few games unfold before you make your first wager.
    </string>
</resources>